Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG 37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries B: 1/4 Inch Reels
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" II Copy, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" III Copy, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Rationalization and Civilization I Master, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Rationalization and Civilization II Master, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Rationalization and Civilization III Master, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Rationalization and Civilizaton IV Master, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Rationalization and Civilization V Master, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Rationalization and Civilization VI Master, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Rationalization and Civilization VII Master, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Rationalization and Civilization I Copy, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Rationalization and Civilization II Copy, 16-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Rationalization and Civilization III Copy, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Rationalization and Civilization IV Copy, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Rationalization and Civilization V Copy, 18-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Rationalization and Civilization VI Copy, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Rationalization and Civilization VII Copy, 17-Mar-78 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - James Lecture: Charles Rosen "Memory in Romantic Song Cycles", 26-Oct-78; RG37.4-JL-30 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - James Lecture: Roland Barthes "Biography and Creativity", 6-Nov-78; RG37.4-JL-31 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Robert L. Heilbroner, 8-Feb-79 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Charles Lindblom I, 22-Feb-79 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Charles Lindblom II, 22-Feb-79 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Gallatin Lecture: N.Z. Davies, 18-Mar-79 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Quentin Anderson, 22-Mar-79 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - James Lecture: V.S. Naipul Reading from his novel "A Bend in the River", 24-Apr-79 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - James Lecture: Dame Frances Yates, 8-May-79 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Humanities Council: Dr. Arnaldo Momigliano, 15-May-79 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - James Lecture: Jean Starobinski, 22-May-79 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later, 27-Sept-79-29-Sept-79 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later, 27-Sept-77-29-Sept-77 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later, 27-Sept-77-29-Sept-77 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Movies as False Sociology I, 13-Oct-79 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Movie as False Sociology II, 13-Oct-79 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - James Lecture: Theodore Zedlin "What Should Intellectuals Do?", 6-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - James Lecture: Paul Ricouer "Is History Still Narrative", 15-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Ross Institute Conference, 27-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Architecture of Confinement I, 28-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Architecture of Confinement II, 28-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - James Lecture: Joseph Brodsky, 21-Nov-79 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Architecture of Confinement Series 2 I, 12-Dec-79 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Architecture of Confinement Series 2 II, 12-Dec-79 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Censorship and Writers I, 1-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Censorship and Writers II, 1-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Censorship and Writers I, 2-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Censorship and Writers II, 2-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Censorship and Writers III, 2-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Censorship and Writers IV, 2-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Lawrence Stone "Revival of Narrative", 20-Feb-80 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - James Lecture: Bernard Williams "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom" I, 20-Mar-80 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - James Lecture: Bernard Williams "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom" III, 20-Mar-80 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - James Lecture: Bernard Williams "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom" IV, 20-Mar-80 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Humanities I: Australian Poets, 24-Apr-80 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Humanitites I, 24-Apr-80 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - James Lecture: Stephen Spender, 23-Oct-80 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Culture and the Actor Series: Roger Shattuck "The Prince, The Actor and I: Culture by Histrionics", 30-Oct-80 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Culture and the Actor Series: Roger Shattuck "The Prince, The Actor and I", 30-Oct-80 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - James Lecture: Leszek Kolakowski "The Polish Lesson", 18-Nov-80 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - James Lecture: Victor Turner "The Actor in Everyday Life", 19-Nov-80 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - James Lecture: Hagemas: Modernity vs Post-Modernity, 4-Mar-81 (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Vonovich Lecture, 21-Apr-81 (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Gallatin Lecture: June Goodfield I, 23-Apr-1981 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Gallatin Lecture: June Goodfield II, 23-Apr-81 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Jane Kramer, 7-May-81 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - De Tocqueville I, 11-May-1981 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - De Tocqueville II, 11-May-1981 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Discussion with Cseslaw Miloscz I, 22-Sept-1981 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Discussion with Cseslaw Miloscz II, 22-Sept-1981 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - James Lecture Series: Hans Magnus Enzensberger "On Consistency", 6-Oct-1981 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard I, 22-Jan-82 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard II, 22-Jan-82 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard III, 22-Jan-82 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard IV, 22-Jan-82 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Gallatin Lectures: Lukas Foss "New American Music Series", 15-Apr-1982 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Gallatin Lectures: Steve Reich "New American Music Series", 21-Apr-1982 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Gallatin Lectures: Philip Glass "New American Music Series", 29-Apr-1982 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - James Lecture: "Jorge Luis Borges in Conversation" I, 29-Sept-1982 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - James Lecture: "Jorge Luis Borges in Conversation" II, 29-Sept-1982 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Nadine Gordimer Humanities Lecture, 14-Oct-1982 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Amartya Sen "Economic Rights", 15-Nov-1982 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Sir Edmond Leach, 25-Feb-83 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Undefined I, 30-Mar-83 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Undefined II, 30-Mar-83 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Edward Stankiewicz: Jakobsen as Structural Linguist and Slavist, 28-Apr-1983 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Henbert Blau "Barthes and Beckett" The Pensum and Punctum", 19-May-83 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Richard Howard and Marshall Blonsky "A Conversation on Residual Barthes", 19-May-83 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Roland Barthes Fesitval: Richard Howard and Marshal Blonsky "A Conversation on Residual Barthes", 19-May-83 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Domna Stanton "The Mater of the Text" Philippe Roger "Portrait of the Artist as 'Gide mangeant une poire" Lawrence Kritzman "Barthesian Free Play", 19-May-83 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Domna Stanton "The Mater of the Text" Philippe Roger "Portrait of the Artist as 'Gide mangeant une poire" Lawrence Kritzman "Barthesian Free Play", 19-May-83 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" I, 20-Oct-83 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" II, 20-Oct-83 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy", 20-Oct-83 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: "Barthes and the Visual Arts" Round table discussion with Dore AShton, Richard Avedon, Annette Michelson, Richard Sennett, Edmund White, 18-May-84 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: "Barthes and the Visual Arts" Roundtable discussion with Dore Ashton, Richard Avedon, Annette Michelson, Richard Sennett, Edmund White, 19-May-84 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" I, 6-Feb-85 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" II, 6-Feb-85 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" III, 6-Feb-85 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Times Square Conference I, 26-Oct-90 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Times Square Conference II, 26-10-90 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Times Square Conference III, 26-Oct-90 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Russian Cons Eve I, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Russian Cons Eve II, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - AM I, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - AM II, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - AM III, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Glasnost PM I, 21-Mar-1991 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Glasnost PM II, 21-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Morning I, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Morning II, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - PM I, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - PM II, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Glasnost AM I, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Glasnost Eve I, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Glasnost AM II, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Glasnost Eve II, 22-Mar-91 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Mini Disks
    - Greenblatt, 1-Oct-04 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Canall, 22-Oct-04 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Nafisi, 3-Dec-04 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Pete Hamill, Undated (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Franzier, Undated (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Electick, Undated (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Post Electick, Undated (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Satrapi, Undated (Box 76, Folder 31)